theflyfishingforum.com 2009-05-09

# NAFFF Privacy Policy - Fish&Fly North American Fly Fishing Forum

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

**Information Collection and Use**  
The North American Fly Fishing Forum (NAFFF) is deeply committed to protecting the privacy of our Internet users. NAFFF is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. For example, we will not sell your e-mail address to any third party or divulge your address to vendors. 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial vBulletin procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Public Forums**  
This site makes forums and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information. In addition, users have the option (when posting to the forums) to be notified when there are replies, which, if chosen will send you e-mail notification of any replies.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small data file containing certain information and is written to your hard drive when you visit the website. A cookie cannot be read by a website other than the one that sets the cookie. Most cookies last only through a single session or visit.

Currently, NAFFF only offers cookies to registered users, in order to retain login information throughout user sessions. Browsers can be configured to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. We also use outside Ad agencies to display default (unsold inventory) banners on our site. These ads may contain cookies that are collected by them, and we do not have direct access to such information. Please see the "Third Parties" section of this document.

**Third Parties**  
NAFFF works with third parties that serve ads to this site. Often, advertisers will employ a third-party measurement service other than NAFFF for tracking the performance of an ad program. We review the privacy policies of companies we work with; however, in these instances, we have no control over the information collected by the third-party, and may not be held responsible for the actions of the third-party measurement service where collected information is concerned. If you have questions regarding different third-party measurement services and their respective methods of information collection, please contact our webmaster. For your convenience, following are links and privacy statements of such third parties:

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may share aggregated traffic information (such as number of unique users, page views, or time spent on our site) with outside sources. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

**Our Commitment to Children's Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**How You Can Access or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by accessing your account from theflyfishingforum.com home page. Click UserCP and then click Edit Profile. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**Notification of Changes**  
All changes to our Privacy Policy will be posted in this Privacy statement so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Regardless of later updates, we will never use the information you submit under this current policy in a new way without providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prevent that use.

**Contacting the Website**  
If you wish to learn more about our efforts to protect your privacy, please feel free to send questions and comments to the Site Administrator: [info@theflyfishingforum.com](mailto:info@theflyfishingforum.com)
